You 're really childish .
Why are you still telling ghost stories at your age ?
I heard that telling ghost stories during the seventh lunar month
will attract spirits .
You 're doomed then .
You 'll be the first target since you 're so fat .
That 's not funny .
Do you guys know why
the term 23.59 is used frequently in the army ?
That 's because midnight is the most evil part of the night .
If someone dies at 23.59 sharp
his soul will not rest in peace
and will return to the mortal world .
And do you know that in this very bunk
a recruit actually committed suicide at 23.59 ?
This bunk ? Are you sure ?
Three years ago , in this very bunk
there was a very effeminate recruit called Lye .
Damn . What is this sissy doing in our camp ?
Haven 't you any shame ?
Listen up .
If you get us into trouble with the sergeant again , you 'll be dead .
Do you hear me ?
You 're shameless . Let 's go .
Are you sure it happened in this bunk ?
Do you think I would joke about this ?
You must be an idiot to believe what he just said .
You see this idiot ?
His face is paler than my buttocks .
Hey .
Are you okay ?
I 'm just feeling slightly sick .
Just admit that you 're a coward and stop acting sick .
Hey , Dragon , that 's enough .
Don 't listen if you 're a coward .
Do you know that there 's a Kuntilanak on this island ?
When a pregnant woman commits suicide
it 's believed that her spirit will return as a Kuntilanak .
It 's an extremely vicious and evil spirit .
Whatever happens , don 't remove your hand
or the spirit will not return to its own world .
May I know if you 're in this room now ?
Can you tell me if you 're in this room now ?
Yes
Don 't let go .
Could you please leave ?
No
Shit .
Shit !
What did they see ?
It was so horrifying that I wouldn 't dare to talk about it .
I heard that once , it entered the body of a pregnant woman
and possessed her unborn daughter .
Every night at 23.59 , this girl would ...
Darn . What 's wrong with you ?
What 's your problem ? Bring it on .
Hey , do you really think you 're a gangster ?
Grow up , man .
Do you think you 're phenomenal just because you 're a platoon leader
and an army scholar ?
Calm down , guys . It was unintentional .
Unintentional ?
How much trouble has he gotten us into ?
Go to hell , you saboteur .
Are you okay ?
Of course he 's okay . He does a great job faking it .
Since you get so freaked out by ghost stories
you shouldn 't have joined the army .
Just be a sissy boy .
Your mouth stinks . Can 't you just zip it ?
Cut it out . You 'd better check on him . Go on .
Yes , your girlfriend 's gone to the toilet .
You 'd better go clean up after him . What a coward .
Are you okay ?
You really need to get your act together .
Look at you .
This has always been your response since we were kids .
This is our last week here .
We can leave this place once the training is completed .
- I 'm really trying , but ... - Just trying isn 't enough .
I really saw something that night .
There you go again . Stop talking about that night .
I can swear .
Is that even necessary ?
It happened at midnight , like what Dragon said .
Now , it 's coming back for me .
Tan !
Snap out of it .
Everyone out there thinks you 're the saboteur in this platoon .
Do you like that title ?
If you don 't , stop going around telling lame ghost stories .
Nobody 's buying that .
They 'll just see you as an idiot . Do you understand ?
Look , take this tap for example . The only problem is that it 's faulty .
It 's as simple as that .
But everyone would rather believe this toilet is haunted , right ?
Wow , you two are so lovey-dovey even in the toilet ?
Please carry on . Don 't mind us .
Your mouth 's as stinky as the toilet bowl .
Please brush your teeth .
Your daddy 's on the phone , asking you to drink your milk .
You 'd better go to the office to answer his call .
Let 's go or we 'll die from the stench here .
Darn , he 's such a coward .
- She 's here ! - Who ?
- She 's here to kill me . - There 's no one inside .
You probably scratched yourself while struggling .
Who did this ?
Own up now if you dare ! Who did this ?
Relax . Can 't you take a joke ?
Do you think this is your grandfather 's house
and that you can joke about anything ?
Scum , scold me for all you like , but leave my grandfather out of this .
I 'd rather kill myself if I were your grandfather .
So you want to be a hero ?
No .
But those who don 't brush their teeth get on my nerves .
- What ? - Bring it on !
Stop ! I said stop !
Sergeant Kuah 's coming .
Room !
What are you doing ?
Nothing , Sergeant . It was just ...
Just feeling deprived as you haven 't had a girl in a long time ?
So now , you 're fooling around with one another , right ?
Very good . You have a lot of energy .
Do you want to walk thirty kilometres tomorrow ?
- No , Sergeant ! - No , Sergeant !
Don 't you guys ever learn ?
I 've already told you that this is the seventh lunar month .
All the spirits will be out for food . Sleep early and don 't be noisy .
Are you pretending not to understand ?
- No , Sergeant ! - No , Sergeant !
Can you stand properly ? Is your other leg crippled ?
Do you think I look too kind to punish you ?
- No , Sergeant . - You ?
No , Sergeant .
Last warning .
Stop fighting or the two of you won 't be able to graduate .
Do you understand ?
- Yes , Sergeant . - Yes , Sergeant .
I cannot hear you .
- Yes , Sergeant ! - Yes , Sergeant !
Switch off the lights and sleep now !
What is this ? Are you putting on an act ?
No , Sergeant .
Last week , you did eleven pull-ups . Today , you can 't even do one .
Is your bottom swollen or too heavy ?
Up .
Try again !
Sir .
Look , I 've got something important to show you .
What ? What is this ?
The date for the route march is extremely inauspicious .
So what are you suggesting ? We cancel the route march ?
Sir , I meant we should postpone the route march and not cancel it .
But of course , cancelling it will be better .
Do you know what you 're talking about ?
How many years have you spent in this camp ?
Don 't you know the importance of the route march ?
Do you think you can cancel it at your whim and fancy ?
Sir , I 'm just worried about our recruits .
Are you worried about the recruits or are you just trying to skive ?
Sir , don 't put it that way .
Kuah , how many more years do you want to be stuck in your position ?
Do you want to be a sergeant forever ?
Just make sure the recruits are ready for the route march .
Do you understand ?
Yes , Sir .
Caucasian wannabe , you didn 't have to make fun of me
even if you didn 't believe me .
Tan .
Tan ?
What 's wrong ?
Nothing .
It 's time for the route march .
I don 't feel well .
Are you sick ?
You 're fine .
I have a bad feeling about this .
What bad feeling ?
She will come for me again .
Who ?
I 've told you before , it 's that woman who ...
Tan . Can you come to your senses ?
I 've told you many times , there 's no woman .
Jeremy , I really saw something . You can ask Chester about it .
That 's enough .
All I know is that if you don 't go for this route march
you won 't be able to graduate .
Do you really want everyone to treat you like a loser ?
I 'm not a loser .
They think you are .
Do you think so too ?
That 's not the point .
I 'm not a loser .
I know what I saw .
All right . What did you see ?
It has a woman 's body ...
but its face ...
Tan .
You didn 't see anything .
How do you know ?
There aren 't any ghosts in this world .
How do you know that ?
I can tell that you have the third eye
which allows you to communicate with the underworld .
But it was all a lie . I didn 't have any third eye .
My father was just a conman
cheating people out of their hard-earned money .
I miss you .
Your wife says she misses you .
Uncle ! Are you all right ?
That old man died believing that I was possessed by his wife 's spirit .
What about your dad ?
To me , I don 't even have a father .
You really haven 't seen any ghosts , have you ?
Not even once .
Do you still want to go for the route march ?
Let 's go .
- We 're ready to go ! - We 're ready to go !
I never knew there was such a beautiful girl on this island .
Haven 't you seen her before ?
She grew up on this island and sells food in our canteen .
So you 've been eyeing her for a long time , haven 't you ?
Cut the crap .
Stop whistling !
That 's my girlfriend , okay ?
Okay , platoon , listen up .
This is your last route march .
It 's very important to everyone and it 's also very tough .
Anyone who isn 't feeling well had better fall out now .
Anyone ?
Good .
You have to take this route march seriously .
While you 're out in the jungle
do not call your buddies ' names unnecessarily .
I 've got some powerful talismans
given by a powerful medium at a powerful temple .
Pass them down .
Take one each and put it in your pocket .
It will ward off evil .
Don 't be stubborn .
This isn 't a joke .
Trust me .
Okay , platoon , listen up .
Are you ready ?
- Yes , Sergeant ! - Yes , Sergeant !
- So what are you waiting for ? - Christmas , Sergeant !
Cut the crap . Whole lot , left turn .
Move on .
Left , left , left , right .
Training to be soldiers
Fight for our land
Once in our lives
Two years of our time
Have you ever wondered
Why must we serve
Because we love our land
And we want it to be free , to be free
Are you okay ?
I 'm exhausted .
Let me help you carry this .
Wow , since we can bring our maids to the army
I should 've told mine to come along to carry my field pack .
Dragon , can you shut up ?
Why should I shut up ? I 'll speak as I please .
I 'm not a weakling who does all your bidding .
Darn . Do you think this is your grandfather 's camp ?
This is really his grandfather 's camp .
His grandfather used to be the camp commander here .
Darn . What 's your point ?
So what if he 's born with a silver spoon in his mouth ?
- What ? - I doubt he can carry on .
This is what you call a sissy . He can 't even roll with the punches .
What the hell .
Auntie , it 's getting late . You should go home .
Be careful .
I can 't locate Tan and Jeremy . Both of you , wait here for them .
I 'm going to find Sergeant Kuah , all right ?
What 's his problem ? He 's being overzealous .
That 's not being overzealous . It 's called bootlicking .
It 's a skill which the nerds have hone to perfection .
I heard his father is a full colonel
and his elder brother was a best recruit
awarded with the Sword of Honour .
His family is really outstanding .
And what 's your point again ? Unlike you , I 'm not a busybody .
What 's taking them so long ?
I hope they 're fine .
What do you mean ?
What 's the time now ?
It 's eleven ...
Was that 23.59 story true ?
Do you think I would joke about something like this ?
Have you heard about the story on this island ?
What story ?
On this island , there was a very powerful medium
who could communicate with the dead .
And it was even said that she could control their spirits .
On that night , she gave birth to a deformed baby .
It was said that the baby was possessed by the spirit she summoned .
That must 've been terrible .
The worst had yet to come .
Do you know what the baby grew into ?
Yes .
Freak !
- Get lost . - Go to hell .
Go away ! Get back to where you came from .
What happened to her subsequently ?
I don 't know .
Some people said she died , but her spirit lingers on the island .
This island ?
Did you hear that ?
Namo Amitabha .
- What are you chanting ? - Namo Amitabha .
- What are you chanting ? Teach me . - Namo Amitabha !
Namo Amitabha .
- Namo Amitabha . - Namo Amitabha .
What are you doing ?
What the hell . You freaked us out .
- Where is Tan ? - Wasn 't he with you ?
I thought he was with you guys .
Put on your helmet ! Where is Tan ?
- He went missing . - Missing ? Where was he last seen ?
I think it was near the fourth checkpoint .
Shit .
Fourth checkpoint ? Was he carrying the talisman I gave him ?
No .
Come on , let 's go look for him . Come on , follow me .
- Sergeant ! - What is it ?
It 's a field pack .
Okay , recruits , listen up .
The four of you , go look for Tan , but don 't wander too far away .
We 'll gather here in five minutes .
- Yes , Sergeant . - Yes , Sergeant .
Shit .
Shit . I can 't see anything !
Okay , recruits , listen up .
Find your buddy and put your left hand on his left shoulder .
Over here .
Okay , number off !
One .
Two .
Three .
Four .
Five .
Five ?
What 's going on ? What 's going on ?
Get up . What 's going on ?
I saw him .
Who did you see ?
- Tan . - Tan ?
Everybody , go and find Tan !
Go .
Tan .
Sergeant !
Kuah , about your report
I don 't understand what you 're trying to tell me .
Sorry , Sir , I know that I can 't write good English .
Yes . We all know that , but that 's not the point .
Based on what you wrote , " Someone saw Tan standing behind him
and ten seconds more , find his body near a tree . "
- Is that right ? - Yes , Sir .
That night , I had a feeling something was out there .
What do you mean by something ?
I don 't know what exactly it was , but it was something like a ghost
a demon , a spirit or , as the Hokkiens put it
something unholy .
Kuah , do you know what you 're talking about ?
Are you blaming Recruit Tan 's accident
on some kind of ghost , on the supernatural ?
I 'm not sure if it was a ghost that killed Tan .
But I can confirm that his death wasn 't an accident .
If it wasn 't an accident , it 's your fault .
My fault ?
Kuah , your responsibility was to keep the recruits safe .
You didn 't do a good job .
Do you know how hard it is to look into the parents ' eyes
and to tell them that their son died in our care ?
In our care !
Anyway , I did my best .
I even brought them talismans from a temple .
Would other sergeants do that for the recruits ?
Giving the recruits talismans couldn 't have kept them safe .
Making sure that they were physically well
doing proper headcounts
and making sure they had enough water to drink
should 've been the way to keep the recruits safe .
I did the headcount and there was an extra recruit . So ?
If there was an extra recruit , that was your fault .
Don 't blame it on the supernatural .
Okay . Anyway , I know I 've done what was necessary .
If the army doesn 't believe in the supernatural
why isn 't there any training on Thursday nights ?
And why aren 't we allowed to walk through Muslim cemeteries
during the route march ?
Just because we don 't do Thursday night route marches
just because we don 't walk through Muslim cemeteries
does that mean we believe in the supernatural ?
You 're kind of simple-minded , aren 't you ?
I don 't know what you mean .
I just know that one recruit has died and I can 't afford to lose another .
In that case , make sure that doesn 't happen again .
Give the recruits half a day off .
If any one of them is still affected psychologically
send him to the medical officer . Do you understand ?
Yes , Sir !
Hey , bro .
Have a bite .
Stop brooding over it .
It was just an accident . No one expected it to happen .
It wasn 't an accident .
What do you mean ?
Like I said many times , I really saw Tan 's spirit .
Tan 's death was definitely not an accident .
I found it strange that
all our torchlights went out at the same time .
I ran a check . All of them were out of juice .
I just changed the batteries .
Do you think that extra headcount was normal ?
Perhaps we panicked and counted wrongly .
You kept saying that you saw Tan 's spirit .
But why didn 't the rest of us see him ?
How the hell would I know ?
Why do you refuse to believe that I saw Tan 's spirit ?
That 's because you caused his death
and you 're afraid he 'll come back to take revenge on you , right ?
- Say that again if you dare ! - What ?
- Try saying that again ! - Calm down , guys . Cut it out .
That 's enough !
We 'll know if it was an accident after the investigation .
What 's the use of an investigation if they 're blind to the truth ?
Listen , I 'm warning you guys now .
It 's better to put coins under the bed .
Otherwise , if your bed shakes at night
it 's not my problem .
Tan .
I 'm sorry .
Tan ?
Tan .
Room .
At ease .
Your mum just called .
She informed us that your dad had just passed away .
Do you need compassionate leave ?
That won 't be necessary .
Are you sure ?
You don 't have to go for the morning training later .
I can manage .
Are you okay ?
- What 's the matter ? - I 'm not feeling well .
Can you book out to visit me ?
This is an army camp .
Do you think I can book out at my whim and fancy ?
Just make an exception this time .
No way .
Tan .
I hope you can rest in peace .
We 're in different worlds now .
I hope you can be more relaxed over there .
Don 't come back for us .
Tan .
I 'm sorry .
I didn 't mean to bully you .
Like you , I always got bullied
when I was a kid .
I thought that if I bullied you , you 'd become stronger and more manly .
But now , I know I was wrong .
I 've realised how silly I was .
Can you please forgive me ?
What ?
I 've reached my limit .
Darn . You 're really weak .
Lim , let me ask you .
Does my mouth really stink ?
Go to hell .
Who are you ?
Jeremy ?
Jeremy .
Are you okay ?
- Did you see her ? - Who ?
Did you see her ?
It 's that woman . She was there on the night Tan died .
Don 't go in there , Jeremy !
Did Tan 's spirit come back for you ?
It was just a dream .
You can 't deny their existence
just because you don 't believe in them .
So you can confirm their existence
just because you believe in them ?
Chester ?
Chester , stop it .
Chester , stop it !
Stop it , Chester !
Tan ?
Are you Tan ?
Hold his head .
Kuah , the recruits can see you .
Sir , it 's really bad this time . Trust me .
So what are you suggesting ?
I think we should call in a medium .
Medium ? Are you serious ?
Yes , Sir . I know a very popular medium .
Kuah , do you realise what you 're saying ?
You want to call in a medium to perform a ritual ?
Sir , it 's not about performing any ritual .
The medium will just be here to take a look .
Just to take a look ? Does this look like a joke to you ?
What kind of signals are you sending to the recruits ?
That this camp is haunted ?
The recruits are not blind .
Having seen Chester 's behaviour , they know what 's going on .
Look . It 's obvious they 're not taking Tan 's death very well .
They 're mentally and emotionally disturbed . I get it .
You 're the platoon sergeant .
You should be looking into this sort of things .
Sir , Chester didn 't lose his mind . I 'm serious . Trust me , okay ?
I 've trusted you before .
Sir , I know you blame me for Lye and Tan 's deaths , right ?
Tan 's death is still under investigation .
Don 't go there .
But as for Lye , he committed suicide .
You know that , I know that .
We could 've saved him had you sent him
for counselling much earlier .
Okay , Sir . It was all my fault .
It was all my fault that Lye and Tan died , okay ?
But this time round
I can 't let the same thing happen to my recruits again , Sir .
Sorry , Sir .
If you want to charge me and jail me in the detention barracks
go ahead .
This time round , I insist on calling in the medium .
Sorry , Sir .
- Sir . - Sir .
Out of all the people here
why was Chester the only one affected ?
Maybe he was just down on his luck .
Talking to you is like talking to a brick wall .
Do you remember the night when Chester and Tan were on guard duty ?
After that night , Tan became really timid .
I dreamt of Tan after the mishap .
And in my dream , Chester died .
I believe he had something to do with Tan 's death .
Are you okay ?
Was it really Tan ?
- What are you talking about ? - I 'm asking if it was Tan .
- How would I know ? - Stop giving me that excuse .
Tell me honestly .
Did you have anything to do with Tan 's death ?
No .
When are you going to stop lying ?
He was your good friend and my best friend too .
He helped you so many times , which I 'm sure you 're aware of .
Don 't you think you 've let him down ?
Chester , tell me what you know . I 'll help you .
Why did you bring me here ?
That night , when Tan and I were on guard duty ...
Chester , how did we get here ?
Are we lost ?
Don 't worry .
We should be able to find a way out if we head in that direction .
Let 's go .
What 's wrong ?
- I 've got a cramp in my leg . - What 's your problem now ?
We still have to hurry to the next checkpoint .
I really can 't go on .
I 'll take a look around . You can take a rest here .
Chester !
Chester , something 's grabbing my leg !
It didn 't look human .
What do you mean ? Think carefully .
- Was there blood or ... - I really don 't know .
I panicked and couldn 't see clearly .
Where did it happen ?
Just down the slope .
Let 's go down and search around .
Jeremy .
It happened here .
Let 's continue searching .
What 's wrong ?
Did you see her ?
Who ?
She was just standing here .
There 's no one else here .
I 'm sure she had something to do with Tan 's death .
I 'm sure it 's her .
Jeremy .
Are you all right ?
I must find her .
Let 's return to the company line first .
- Come on . - Chester .
You could be the next fatality .
What are you talking about ?
I dreamt of you dying .
Dream ?
It was only a dream .
Before Tan died , I dreamt of his demise too .
Both dreams were exactly the same .
I 've got to find that woman .
I believe the villagers on this island should know her .
Excuse me .
You grew up on this island , didn 't you ?
Yes . Why ?
There 's a legend about a medium on this island .
Is that true ?
- I don 't know . - I believe you do .
This is very important to us . Please tell us .
She has killed a friend of mine .
I really don 't know .
He may be the next fatality .
He 'll die if you don 't tell us the truth .
Please help us .
All right ?
I saw her when I was a kid .
- Go to hell . - Go to hell .
- Freak ! - Get lost !
Go away !
One by one , the kids in the village started dying .
Everyone believed that it was Madam Yi
who placed a curse on the kids
so as to seek revenge for her daughter .
But I couldn 't be sure .
Looking at her , I could sense her fury and viciousness .
She seemed to have a strange supernatural ability
to control other people .
Is she still living on the island ?
I haven 't seen her in a long time .
But according to some villagers who saw her recently
she has gone insane .
Do you know where she lives ?
On the north side of this island somewhere near the river .
Let 's talk to Sergeant Kuah .
Thank you .
Chester .
Chester !
Do you believe now ?
Stop .
Don 't be afraid .
Help me .
Help me !
Why did you have to kill them ?
That was just an accident .
I didn 't kill them .
So who did ?
I 'm sorry .
I 've let you down .
Darn .
We 're stuck here for this weekend .
Don 't get me started .
My girlfriend 's going to be peeved again .
Have you heard about the history of this island ?
What history ?
It was said that there were two recruits
who accidentally killed a villager while performing guard duties .
Were there villagers on this island ?
Of course . Didn 't you study history ?
There used to be many villagers on this island .
That villager 's spirit came back and took revenge on the two recruits .
Every night at 23.59 , she would return to haunt them .
Are you sure ?
Do you think I would joke about something like this ?
Give me a break .
That story happened so long ago . I can confirm it was just a rumour .
Do you know why I can confirm it 's true ?
Why ?
It was my uncle who told me .
- Who is your uncle ? - Who is your uncle ?
He 's the commander of this camp .
- Our commander ? - Our commander ?